let questions25 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "to circulate",
      answer: "D. verbreiten",
      options: [
        "A. sammeln",
        "B. wiederholen",
        "C. konzentrieren",
        "D. verbreiten"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "consequent",
      answer: "B. folgerichtig",
      options: [
        "A. unerwartet",
        "B. folgerichtig",
        "C. zufällig",
        "D. spontan"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "to derive",
      answer: "C. ableiten",
      options: [
        "A. erfinden",
        "B. verschlüsseln",
        "C. ableiten",
        "D. zerstören"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "to drown",
      answer: "A. ertrinken",
      options: [
        "A. ertrinken",
        "B. schwimmen",
        "C. tauchen",
        "D. segeln"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "dynasty",
      answer: "D. Herrschergeschlecht",
      options: [
        "A. Parlament",
        "B. Revolution",
        "C. Regierung",
        "D. Herrschergeschlecht"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "fraction",
      answer: "B. Bruchteil",
      options: [
        "A. Ganzes",
        "B. Bruchteil",
        "C. Maximum",
        "D. Gesamtheit"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "frost",
      answer: "C. Raureif",
      options: [
        "A. Sonnenschein",
        "B. Hitze",
        "C. Raureif",
        "D. Regen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "illusion",
      answer: "A. Täuschung",
      options: [
        "A. Täuschung",
        "B. Wahrheit",
        "C. Realität",
        "D. Wirklichkeit"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "to invade",
      answer: "B. erobern",
      options: [
        "A. verteidigen",
        "B. erobern",
        "C. beschützen",
        "D. verhandeln"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "lieutenant",
      answer: "C. Stellvertreter",
      options: [
        "A. General",
        "B. Soldat",
        "C. Stellvertreter",
        "D. Kommandant"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "marine",
      answer: "D. marin",
      options: [
        "A. terrestrisch",
        "B. luftgebunden",
        "C. unterirdisch",
        "D. marin"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "merit",
      answer: "B. Verdienst",
      options: [
        "A. Fehler",
        "B. Verdienst",
        "C. Mangel",
        "D. Schwäche"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "navy",
      answer: "A. Kriegsmarine",
      options: [
        "A. Kriegsmarine",
        "B. Landarmee",
        "C. Luftwaffe",
        "D. Geheimdienst"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "polar",
      answer: "C. polar",
      options: [
        "A. tropisch",
        "B. gemäßigt",
        "C. polar",
        "D. subtropisch"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "ray",
      answer: "D. Strahl",
      options: [
        "A. Wolke",
        "B. Dunkelheit",
        "C. Schatten",
        "D. Strahl"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to resign",
      answer: "B. kündigen",
      options: [
        "A. beginnen",
        "B. kündigen",
        "C. aufnehmen",
        "D. weitermachen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "suicide",
      answer: "C. Selbstmord",
      options: [
        "A. Heilung",
        "B. Leben",
        "C. Selbstmord",
        "D. Genesung"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "to tremble",
      answer: "A. zittern",
      options: [
        "A. zittern",
        "B. tanzen",
        "C. springen",
        "D. laufen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "underlying",
      answer: "B. zugrunde liegend",
      options: [
        "A. offensichtlich",
        "B. zugrunde liegend",
        "C. oberflächlich",
        "D. eindeutig"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "via",
      answer: "C. über",
      options: [
        "A. unter",
        "B. neben",
        "C. über",
        "D. entlang"
      ]
    }
];

export default questions25;